I'm Peppa Pig
This is my
little brother George
This is Mummy Pig
And this
is Daddy Pig
Peppa Pig
Grumpy Rabbit'
s hovercraft
Grandpa Pig is taking Peppa and George out for the day on his sailing boat
Hello，Grandpa Pig
Hello
Hello，old bean
Grandpa？
That man just
called you an old bean？
Yes，Peppa
it's another way
of saying old friend
Are they
your friends
Grandpa？
Oh，not really
We're just
members of the same sailing club
Now
where did I
leave my boat？
What does your
boat look like
Grandpa？
It has a little
red flag on top of the mast
Like that
little flag？
Ah，yes
Oh dear
Grandpa Pig's
sailing boat has sunk
I'm afraid we can'
t go sailing today
children
Here is Grumpy
Rabbit on his hovercraft
What is that
monstrosity？
Is it a boat or
a sailing clock？
Hello， What a marvellous day for sailing， Hello， Grumpy Rabbit， Peppa
you look sad
what's
the matter？
We can't
go sailing
because our
boat has sunk
Oh dear
why don't you
hop onto my hovercraft？
Hooray， I really
don't think this is quite…
Hold on to
your hats
Grumpy Rabbit's
hovercraft can go on land and water
I built it myself
You'd never guess， would you？ We don't need that bit
You can't drive
this thing around here
You're not a
member of the sailing club
But you're a member， aren't you？ Yes， but that's all right then
Nothing like a
peaceful day sailing
The calmness
of the water
And the
quietness of the…
What's that
horrible noise？
Hello there
Lovely day
for a sail
It's that
monstrosity again
Is that
Grandpa Pig？
Uh，hello？
I say
is anybody
else thirsty？
Me，me
I saw an old
shed back there
selling juice
That's not
an old shed
That's the
sailing club cafe
It's for
members only
Yes，whatever
Let's go and
get some juice
Hello there
four beakers
of juice please
I'm afraid you
cannot be served here
sir，Unless you'
re a club member
I'm not，but he is
Uh，hello
four juices please
Ah，yes，sir
This is the life
eh？
The sea
and the sky
And the
boats sailing by？
But the boats
are not sailing by
Grampy Rabbit
There's no wind
without wind
Sailing
boats can't sail
We need to
rescue them
Grumpy Rabbit
Good idea，Peppa
Hold on to
your socks
Ahoy there
Toss me a line
and I'll tow
you back in
Here we go
Randy Rabbit's hovercraft is towing sailing boats back to shore
We're towing
the boats to shore
boys
We're towing
the boats to shore
We're towing the
boats to the car park
Towing the
boats to be parked
I brought
everyone back to the car park
That way
they don't have
so far to walk to their cars
But sailing boats
don't go on land
like hovercrafts
Oh，yes
Grandpa Pig
who is this
friend of yours？
So sorry
about that
Sorry？
About what？
We want to thank
him for rescuing us
Oh，I see
He's called
Grampy Rabbit
Delighted to
meet you， Old Bean
You're
very welcome
Old Bean
Three cheers
for Grampy Rabbit
Hip，hip，hurray
Hip，hip，hip
hurray
巴…巴克